{
    "1": {
        "question" : "What currency is used in the Federation?",
        "answer" : "d",
        "a" : "Gold",
        "b" : "Platinum",
        "c" : "Federation Credits",
        "d" : "Latinum",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "2": {
        "question" : "Where is DS9 located?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "The edge of sector D",
        "b" : "Near a stable worm hole",
        "c" : "Orbiting Earth",
        "d" : "At the center of the Milky Way",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "3": {
        "question" : "Which 'Star Trek: Deep Space Nine' character said 'Doctor, I do believe there's hope for you yet'?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Garak",
        "b" : "Kira Nerys",
        "c" : "Julian Bashir",
        "d" : "Odo",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "3": {
        "question" : "Which 'Star Trek: Deep Space Nine' character said 'Doctor, I do believe there's hope for you yet'?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Garak",
        "b" : "Kira Nerys",
        "c" : "Julian Bashir",
        "d" : "Odo",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "4": {
        "question" : "Who is the highest-ranking Starfleet officer aboard the station?",
        "answer" : "d",
        "a" : "Garak",
        "b" : "Quark",
        "c" : "Julian Bashir",
        "d" : "Benjamin Sisko",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "5": {
        "question" : "Approximately how long did the Cardassian Occupation last?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "50 years",
        "b" : "100 years",
        "c" : "5 years",
        "d" : "10 years",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "6": {
        "question" : "Which DS9 star appears in the movie 'American History X'?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "Edward Furlong",
        "b" : "Avery Brooks",
        "c" : "Edward Norton",
        "d" : "Fairuza Balk",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "7": {
        "question" : "Before the Federation took over Deep Space Nine the Cardassians had occupied it. They called it a different name, what was it?",
        "answer" : "c",
        "a" : "Gul",
        "b" : "Dominion HQ",
        "c" : "Terok Nor",
        "d" : "Bajor",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "8": {
        "question" : "Who occupied the station before the Federation arrived?",
        "answer" : "c",
        "a" : "Romulans",
        "b" : "Orians",
        "c" : "Cardassians",
        "d" : "Kardashians",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "9": {
        "question" : "Jadzia Dax was married to which fellow officer?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Sisko",
        "b" : "Odo",
        "c" : "Worf",
        "d" : "Quark",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "10": {
        "question" : "What is the title of Odo, the head of station security?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Constable",
        "b" : "Officer",
        "c" : "Commander",
        "d" : "Major",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "11": {
        "question" : "In the first season episode 'Babel,' a number of DS9's regular cast contracted a bizarre virus that left them incapable of utilizing language in any way. Which character was NOT afflicted with the virus in this episode?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Quark",
        "b" : "Odo",
        "c" : "Dax",
        "d" : "Sisko",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "12": {
        "question" : "Every incarnation of Star Trek needs its token 'character aging prematurely' episode, but which character became old before their time in DS9?",
        "answer" : "c",
        "a" : "Sisko",
        "b" : "Odo",
        "c" : "Bashir",
        "d" : "Quark",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "13": {
        "question" : " Which actor has appeared in 'DS9' as a Vulcan, a Klingon, a Human and a Changeling?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "J. G. Hertzler",
        "b" : "Rene Auberjonois",
        "c" : "Terry Farrell",
        "d" : "Colm Meaney",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "14": {
        "question" : "Who owns a bar on the station?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "No one - its free bar",
        "b" : "Quark",
        "c" : "Sisko",
        "d" : "Work",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "15": {
        "question" : "What is the military rank of Doctor Julian Bashir?",
        "answer" : "c",
        "a" : "Major",
        "b" : "Ensign",
        "c" : "Lieutenant",
        "d" : "Corpsman",
        "e" : "No rank - he's a doctor"
    },
    "16": {
        "question" : " In the 5th season episode 'In the Cards', Jake Sisko wants to get his dad a special present at an auction run by Quark. Whose rookie baseball card, from 1951, does Jake get for him?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "Hank Aaron",
        "b" : "Willy Mays",
        "c" : "Jackie Robinson",
        "d" : "Barry Bonds",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "17": {
        "question" : " To a member of which species did Garak say 'Well, let me guess! You're either lost, or desperately searching for a good tailor'?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Klingon",
        "b" : "Romulan",
        "c" : "Vulcan",
        "d" : "Human",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    },
    "18": {
        "question" : "What was Dr. Bashir's class rank at Starfleet Academy?",
        "answer" : "b",
        "a" : "1st",
        "b" : "2nd",
        "c" : "3rd",
        "d" : "last",
        "e" : "None - he never graduated"
    },
    "19": {
        "question" : "Who killed Jennifer Sisko?",
        "answer" : "a",
        "a" : "Klingon",
        "b" : "Cardassian",
        "c" : "Borg",
        "d" : "Ferengi",
        "e" : "She died of natural causes"
    },
    "20": {
        "question" : "What race is the chief of security?",
        "answer" : "d",
        "a" : "Klingon",
        "b" : "Borg",
        "c" : "Xindi",
        "d" : "Changling",
        "e" : "None of the above"
    }
}
